Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5583/1
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
0000-2999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
5583/1
120 cubic feet
120 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Publications, manuals, policies, and plans issued by a large sample of Fortune 500 corporations and by a variety of organizations, such as professional and trade associations, government agencies, and educational and cultural organizations. The materials issued by corporations include company histories, employee newsletters, employee benefit plans, personnel practice manuals, performance appraisal forms, affirmative action policies, training brochures, job descriptions, and career development programs as well as national trade association documents and recruitment material.
5697819
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, April 26, 2019
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, June 06, 2019
Scope and Contents
Several economic activities(sectors) are represented in the collection, such as manufacturing, transportation, mining, banking, insurance, utilities, trade, and services. Corporations whose pamphlets are held in the collection include AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Bell Telephone System, Firestone Tire & Rubber, Ford Motor Co., General Electric, General Foods, General Mills, General Motors, Goodyear Tire & Rubber, Heinz, International Harvester, Johnson & Johnson, Lockheed Aircraft Co., Maytag Co., Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., National Association of Manufacturers, Pennsylvania Railroad Co., Radio Corporation of America (RCA), Standard Oil, Tennessee Valley Authority, Union Carbide, and Westinghouse Electric among numerous other corporations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents 5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications 5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
Adult education; Aeronautics; Agricultural industries; Aluminum industry and trade; Airlines; Aircraft industry; Agricultural machinery; Architectural metal-work; Audio equipment industry; Automobile industry and trade; Arbitration, Industrial; Agricultural chemicals industry; Audio equipment industry; Bituminous materials industry; Building trades; Buildings--Environmental engineering; Banks and banking; Breweries; Baked products industry; Business consultants; Clothing trade; Coal mines and mining; Chemical industry; Compressor industry; Clerks (Retail trade); Computer industry; Cereal products; Consumer Protection; Container industry; Credit Unions; Clay industries; Cement industries; Copper alloys; Dairy products industry; Detergent industry; Executives--Training of; Electric power transmission; Electronics industries; Food industry and trade; Frozen foods and industry; Footwear industry; Fruit trade; Farm produce--Marketing--Government policy; Finance, Public; Glass container industry; Glass manufacture; Gas extraction; Grain trade; Grocery trade; Gasket industry; Human capital; Hydroelectric power plants; Life insurance.; Iron industry and trade; Property insurance.; Casualty insurance.; Instructional materials industry; Health insurance.; Investment banking; Infant formula industry; Knit good industry; Labor unions; Local transit; Luggage industry; Logging; Medical supplies industry; Medicaid; Motor vehicle industry; Metal trade; Meat industry and trade; Military vehicle industry; Medical instruments and apparatus industry; Management; Measuring instruments; Natural gas pipelines; Notions (Merchandise); Newspaper publishing; Navigation equipment industry; National security; Office management; Office equipment and supplies; Petroleum refineries; Photographic industry; Paper folding (Graphic design); Public utilities; Paper products industry; Political participation; Plastics industry and trade; Pharmaceutical industry; Paint industry and trade; Public administration; Public opinion polls; Paper bag industry; Retail trade; Rug and carpet industry; Railroads; Rubber industry and trade; Railroad equipment industry; Roller bearings; Security systems industry; Service industries; Social security; Shipment of goods; Sanitary supply industry; Soybean industry; Slaughtering and slaughter-houses; Transportation equipment industry.; Telecommunication.; Trucking industry.; Trucks--Design and construction.; Textile industry.; Trade associations.; Tobacco industry.; Universities and colleges.; Vocational education.; Wood products.; Welding equipment industry.; Woolen goods industry.; A. Philip Randolph Institute.; Abbott Laboratories.; Abbott Laboratories. House Organs.; Abraham & Straus.; Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation.; Administrative Management Society.; Adult Education Association.; Aero Supply Mfg. Co.; Aerojet-General Corporation.; Aeroquip Corporation.; Aerospace Industries Association of America.; Aetna Life Insurance Company (Hartford, Conn.); Affiliated Schools for Workers.; African- American Labor Center.; Agway Inc.; Air Reduction Company.; Air Transport Association of America.; Airlines Negotiating Committee.; Alaska. Department of Administration.Division of Personnel.; Alden's, Inc.; Alexander Smith & Sons, Carpet Co.; Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation.; Allegheny Metal.; Allied Chemical & Dye Corporation; Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company.; Aluminum Company of America.; American Arbitration Association.; American Brake Shoe Company.; American Can Company.; American Labor Education Service.; American Locomotive Company.; American Management Association.; American Merchant Marine Institute.; American Metal Climax, Inc.; American Motors Corporation.; American Petroleum Institute.; American Plan Association.; American Society of Safety Engineers.; American Telephone and Telegraph Company.; American Textile Manufacturers Institute.; American Thread Company.; American Trucking Associations.; American Type Founders Company.; American Vocational Association.; Americans Against Union Control of Government.; Amtrak.; Anaconda American Brass Company.; Anaconda Company.; Anaconda Copper Mining Company.; Anaconda Wire and Cable Company.; Anchor Hocking Glass Corporation.; Armco Steel Corporation.; Armour and Company.; Armstrong Cork Company.; Associated Builders & Contractors (U.S.); Associated General Contractors of America.; Association of American Railroads.; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad Company.; Atlantic Refining Company.; Atlas Chemical Industries.; ATO, Inc.; Automobile Manufacturers Association.; Automotive and Aviation Parts Manufacturers.; Automotive Council for War Production.; Bell & Howell Co.; Bell Aircraft Corporation.; Bell of Pennsylvania.; Bell Telephone Company.; Bell Telephone Laboratories.; Bethlehem Steel Corporation.; Bird and Son, Inc.; Bituminous Coal Operators' Association.; Bloomer Brothers .; Boeing Aerospace Company.; Boeing Company.; Borden Company.; Brockway Glass Company.; Building Trades Employers' Association.; Bureau of National Affairs (Arlington, Va.); Burlington Industries, Inc.; Burndy Engineering Company.; Burrough Corporation.; California Institute of Technology. Industrial Relations Center.; California Institute of Technology.; California State Personnel Board.; Canadian National Railways; Canadian Pacific Railway Company.; Carborundum Company (Niagara Falls, N.Y.); Carnation Company.; Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation.; Carrier Corporation.; Caterpillar Tractor Company.; Celanese Corporation.; Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corporation.; Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America.; Chemical Corn Exchange Bank.; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company.; Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Maryland.; Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia.; Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company.; Chessie System, inc.; Chicago Transit Authority.; Chrysler Corporation.; Cincinnati Bell Inc.; Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada.; Climax Molybdenum Company.; Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A.; Colgate-Palmolive Company.; Colorado Fuel and Iron Company.; Columbia Gas Company.; Commerce and Industry Association of New York.; Committee for the Nation's Health.; Commonwealth Edison Company.; Communications Workers of America.; Cone Mills Corporation.; Connecticut General Life Insurance Company.; Consolidated Edison Company of New York, inc.; Consolidated Gas, Electric Light, and Power Company of Baltimore.; Consolidated Natural Gas Company.; Consolidated Vultee Aircraft Corporation.; Consumers' League of New York City.; Consumers Power Company (Mich.); Container Corporation of America.; Continental Can Company.; Continental Insurance Company.; Continental Oil Company.; Cooperative League of the U.S.A.; Corn Products Refining Company.; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.; Cornell University.; Corning Glass Works.; Council Against Communist Aggression (U.S.); Council for International Progress in Management (USA); Council of Profit Sharing Industries (U.S.); Crane Co.; Crane Packing Co.; Credit Union National Association.; Crouse-Hinds Company.; Crown Zellerbach Corporation.; Crucible Steel Company of America.; Dan River Mills Inc.; Dartnell Corporation.; Daystrom, inc.; Dartnell Corporation.; Deere & Company.; Detroit Edison Company.; Diamond Alkali Company.; Dictaphone Corp.; Dole Food Company.; Douglas Aircraft Company.; Dow Chemical Company.; E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company.; Eagle Pencil Company.; Eastern Gas and Fuel Associates.; Eastern Western & Southwestern Canier Company.; Eastman Kodak Company.; Eaton Corporation.; Eaton Manufacturing Company.; Ecusta Paper Company.; Electronic Industries Alliance.; Eli Lilly and Company.; Employers' Association of Chicago.; Employers' Association of Detroit.; Employers' Association of Grand Rapids.; Employers' Association of Massachusetts.; Employers' Association of Milwaukee.; Employers' Association of Pittsburgh.; Employers' Association of Washington.; Employers' Group of Insurance Companies.; Employers' Labor Relations Information Committee.; Employers' of Mutual of Wasau.; Engineers Joint Council. Engineering Manpower Commission.; Erie Railroad Company.; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company.; Erlanger Mills, Inc.; Erwin Cotton Mills.; Esso Research and Engineering Company.; Esso Standard Oil Company.; Exxon Corporation; Falstaff Brewing Corporation; Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America; Federal Professional Association (U.S.); Federal Reserve Bank of New York; Federated Employers of San Francisco; Federated Employers of the Bay Area; Fieldcrest Mills Inc.; William Filene's Sons Co.; Firestone Tire and Rubber Company; First National Bank (Ithaca, N.Y.); First National Bank Maryland; First National Bank of Boston; First National Bank of Chicago; First National Bank of Portland (Portland, Me.); First National Bank of St. Louis; First Pennsylvania Bank, N.A.; First Pennsylvania Banking and Trust Company, Philadelphia.; Fischer and Porter Company; Florida Power & Light Company; Ford Foundation; Ford Motor Company; Foster and Forbes Glass Company; Foundation for Economic Education, inc.; General Dynamics Corporation.; General Electric Company; George Fischer, Ltd.; J.N. Adam & Company.; New Jersey Bell Telephone Company.; New York Chamber of Commerce.; Society for Equitable Assurances on Lives and Survivorships.; South Central Bell.; University of California, Berkeley. Institute of Industrial Relations.; William Filene's Sons Co.; Commonwealth Edison Company; A. Philip Randolph Institute; ATO, Inc.; Aero Supply Mfg. Co.; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
5697819
- Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Presentation EEO - Affirmative Action, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Affirmative Action - Practices and Procedures, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Box: 1, Folder: 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: ATO Investor Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Notice of Annual Meeting of Shareholders, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Box: 1, Folder: 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Abbott Topics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Abbott Topics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Box: 1, Folder: 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: AM Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By AM Corporate Communications. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 90 Days; Vol. 3 No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Bruning Division News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: VariTyperNews, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Euclid Plant News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Service; Vol. 2 No. 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: AM Canada News; Vol. 3 No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Multigraphics Division News; Vol. 5 No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Data Systems Dispatch, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: AM News-Corporate Edition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Box: 1, Folder: 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Flyer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: An Invitation to AchieveCertified Administrative Manager, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 3 Ways AMS Can Help, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Roster and Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By AMS - Syracuse Chapter. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Golden PastA Challenging Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Joseph Gawthrop. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Publications, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: One of the greatest assets, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Management World; Vol. 2 No. 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Publications, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Box: 1, Folder: 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: News; Vol. 2 No. 2- Vol. 5 No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Box: 1, Folder: 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Summary of the Study of the Adult Education Assoc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Edmund Brunner. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Lifelong Learning: The Adult Years. Vol. 1 No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Labor Education Section, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: National Adult Continuing Education Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Career Counseling for Adults, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: There is Always Room to Grow, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Box: 1, Folder: 8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: How to Make Unions Unnecessary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Box: 1, Folder: 9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Aerojet Review: Closeup of a Corporate Family, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Box: 1, Folder: 10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 1958 Year Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: 1957 Year Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Group Insurance Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Group Hospitalization Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Group Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Group Disability Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Major Medical Expense Benefits, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: The Good Word, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: The Good Word, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: The Good Word, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: The Good Word, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: The Good Word, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: The Good Word, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: The Good Word, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Inter-Office Communication: Employee Eval., Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By J.T. Kearney. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Employment Forms, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Employees' Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Clerical Rating, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Inter-Office Communication: Vacation Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Henry Beers. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Employment Forms, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Inter-Office Communication: Employee Eval., Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Intro. Of New Employee, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: The Safety Man, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: Physical Exam, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Indoctrination and Orientation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Description of Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Savings Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 33: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: Employee Performance and Development Guide, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 35: Terms of the Group Hospital Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 36: Rating, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 37: Salary Evaluation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 38: Group Insurance Certificate, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 39: Suggestion Form, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 40: The Cooperative Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 41: Cooperative Disability Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 42: Insurance Campaigns, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 43: Farmington Ave. Office: Salaried Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 44: Farmington Ave. Office: Hourly Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 45: Group Insurance Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 46: Group Insurance Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 47: Group Insurance Plan for Retired Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 48: Historical Sketch, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 49: 1959 Year Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Box: 1, Folder: 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Wages and the Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Lois MacDonald. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Flyer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Flyer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Hands Across the Atlantic, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: AALC Reporter; Vol. 2 No. 1-Vol. 14 No. 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Box: 1, Folder: 13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Personnel Manual, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By H.G. Smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Compensation and Payroll, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Changes in Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Work Rules & Regulation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: General, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Labor Union Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Index, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Box: 1, Folder: 14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Agway History Course, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By David Kettler. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Personnel Services, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Box: 1, Folder: 15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefit Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Box: 1, Folder: 16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Guide: Performance, Salary and Development, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Supervisor's Guide: Employee Appraisal Systems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Performance Reviews, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Affirmative Action, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Safety Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Look Forward to Your Retirement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Master Medical Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By S.C. Tarbell. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Careers in Agriculture, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Learn to Manage, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Agway Management Council, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: Performance Review, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Educational Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: Personnel Manual: Management Responsibilities for Labor Union Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By J.C. Piser. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Description of Benefits, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: This is Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Employee Benefit Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Box: 1, Folder: 18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employment Security after Retirement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Box: 1, Folder: 19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Managing the Airspace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Rising Employment Costs in Air Transport, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Facts about the ATA, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Safety Record 1938-1973, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Airlines Mutual Aid Agreement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Box: 1, Folder: 20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Airlines Negotiating Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By Potter Stewart. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Airlines Negotiating Conference: Brief of Public Counsel to the Board, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By James Highsaw, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Airlines Negotiating Conference: Memorandum Brief of International Assoc. of Machinists, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By Clarence Mulholland. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Brief Submitted on Liability of ANC, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By S.G. Tipton. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Articles of Association of ANC, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: ANC Conference Articles of Association and By-Laws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Articles of Association, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Arbitration News Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Box: 1, Folder: 21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Employees, Eighth Edition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Classification and Pay Plan Distribution List, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    By J.S. Frazer. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Public Employees' Retirement System, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Group Health Care & Life Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Class Specification, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Group Health Care & Life Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Personnel Rules, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)